Guide to the American Society of Planning Officials Records, 1925-1982
American Society of Planning Officials Records, 1925-1982
- Series IV. ASPO history of activities (and miscellaneous files)
  - Interprofessional Urban Planning Committee, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Interprofessional Urban Planning Committee, Louis Justement - Washington, D.C., 1948 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Zoning - city, county, rural and agricultural clippings, 1935-1937 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Zoning - city, county, rural and agricultural clippings, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Zoning - city, county, rural and agricultural clippings, 1940-1941 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence regarding membership and requests for publications, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
  - Airport and aviation clippings, 1936-1941 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - National Conference on Planning, 1938-1940 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1935-1941 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - City Planning clippings, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - City Planning clippings, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - City Planning clippings, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - City Planning clippings, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - City Planning clippings, 1935-1937 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Public Administration Clearing House (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 26-28)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1940 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1945 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 33-34)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Public Administration Services, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Public Administration Services-no. 86: "Action for Cities", 1945 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Citizens for Cities (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - National Association of Home Builders, 1955, 1958, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - National Advisory Committee on Air Pollution (Box 20, Folder 8-9)
  - National Council for Community Improvement, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - National Council for Community Improvement, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - National Council for Community Improvement, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - FHA (Federal Housing Administration) (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Housing Division - Public Works Administration, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - National Committee on Recreation Facilities, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Blucher's Articles, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Blucher's Articles, 1941-1942 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Blucher's Articles, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Blucher's Articles, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Blucher's and Terret's Articles, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Blucher's and Terret's Articles, 1946-1947 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Cincinnati, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Foreign (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Foreign A-L, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 24-25)
  - Foreign H-M, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 26-27)
  - Conference on Metropolitan Area Problems, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence Cl-Cr, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 29-30)
  - Correspondence D, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 31-32)
  - Detroit, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Detroit, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence E, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence F, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence G, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence H, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence I, 1945 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - John D. Borah (Box 20, Folder 40-41)
  - Perloff Book: Israel Stollman's File (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Perloff White Papers - reviews (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Harvey S. Perloff, Immediate Past President, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Perloff White Papers - correspondence (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Perloff Whit Papers - Reuss Committee (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Jane Jacobs (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
  - Alfred Bettman Foundation, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 3-4)
  - Alfred Bettman Foundation, 1950-1951 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Alfred Bettman Foundation, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
  - Alfred Bettman Foundation, 1955-1958 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - ASPO Notices and minutes of meetings, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Journal (Daily Office), 1936 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - ASPO Encomium, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - ASPO, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - ASPO, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - ASPO, 1938-1939 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - ASPO, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - ASPO, 1944-1947 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Spellman Fund, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Spellman Fund, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Spellman Fund, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Spellman Fund, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Spellman Fund, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Spellman Fund, 1944 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Spellman Fund, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Bennett - Field service reports, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 25-28)
  - Pomeroy - field service reports, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Pomeroy field trips - A-M, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Pomeroy field trips - N-Z, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Pomeroy, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Pomeroy, 1941 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Pomeroy, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Kramer, Ferd; Orton, etc., 1952-1954 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Servicemen - A-M, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Servicemen - N-Z, 1945 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - ASPO, 1961-1963 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - ASPO - planning advisory service, 1956-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - ASPO - membership analysis and data, 1938-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Membership affiliation (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Membership reports (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Member benefits (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Membership dues (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Book publishing - publications (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Member participation (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Membership promotion (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Members' periodicals (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - I. Planner of the Year, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - II. Planner of the Year, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - III. Planner of the Year, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - IV. Planner of the Year, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Public Administration Service: community, 1960-1961 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Public Administration Service: Public Automated Systems Service, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - URBANDOC special file, 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 19-21)
  - URBANDOC, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 22-23)
  - URBANDOC, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - URBANDOC special file, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 25-29)
  - ASPO minutes, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - ASPO, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - ASPO, 1963-1974 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - ASPO, 1958-1970 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - ASPO, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Draft Deferment (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Policies: Elections and Ballots, Nominee Guidelines (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Endowments; Policy - Endorsement; Ethics (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Field Services (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - ASPO-AIP International Committee, 1963-1973 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - II Policies - Litigation (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - II Policies - Minorities, 1970-1974 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - II Statements on Policies (published), 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Corporation History: Staff, Space, Facilities, 1951-1975 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - II Policies - Students, 1968-1975 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Testimony, Lobbying and Tax (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Training, 1942-1959 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - "Washington Window" (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Policy - Women, 1971-1975 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Zoning Digest and Zoning, 1964-1975 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Original paste-ups (not being used); reproduced and repasted for Handbook, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Urban Policy, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Material Transmitted - Corporate History, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 3-4)
  - Drafts, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Corporate History - Committees (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Audits (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Awards (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - II Policies - Banking, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors (see also policies and appendix) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - II Policies - Budget (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Corporate History: Constitution, By-laws (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - II Policies - ASPO Objectives and Development (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Additional or Substitute Copy post Mar. 1976 mailing; not included in Aug. 1976 pages transmitted (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Corporate History (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Board handbook - printing/binding (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Board handbook (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Corporate History - Activities (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - History of Activities - Distribution (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - History of Activities - Records (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - ASPO (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Music - History (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Research - General (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Publications - material distributed (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - ASPO Audits, 1935-1974 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - ASPO miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Publication sales (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Sponsored research (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Sponsored research - sections (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Spikes - projects - Source (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Policies/History Publications; Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - II Policies - Corporate History (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Education Committee (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Policy - Education (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - II Policy - Personnel (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - School Surveys (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Opportunities in City Planning (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - National Conference - Publicity (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - National Planning Conference miscellany (Box 23, Folder 40-41)
  - II Policies - Organizational Relationships - American Institute of Planners (Box 23, Folder 42-46)
  - Planning Publicity (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - ASPO History - master copy (Box 23, Folder 48-52)
  - ASPO Board - meeting arrangements (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - ASPO Board - possible meeting sites (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Membership - promotion (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Membership - brochures (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - History of Activities - Alfred Bettman Memorial (address by John Lord O'Brien) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - History of Activities - American City Planning Institute (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - History of Activities - ASPO-IRC Training (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - History of Activities - Consultant (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - History of Activities - Consulting work (possible brochure) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - History of Activities - Criticism (general) (Box 24, Folder 10-14)
  - History of Activities - Criticism (Harvard) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - History of Activities - Encomium and Citations (Box 24, Folder 16-17)
  - History of Activities - Film Production (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - History of Activities - ASPO Growth and Development (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - History of Activities - Hammer Washington Service (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - History of Activities - ASPO Impact (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - History of Activities - Indirect Cost Rate Determination, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - History of Activities - Information Systems (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - History of Activities - Insurance (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - History of Activities - Liaison (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - History of Activities - Listing in directories (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - History of Activities - ASPO Lock Box (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - History of Activities - Newsletter (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - History of Activities - Outside Policies (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - History of Activities - Public Service Film Board (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - History of Activities - Questionnaires (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - History of Activities - Research (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - History of Activities - Testimony (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - History of Activities - Training (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - History of Activities - Translators' List (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - History of Activities - Zoning Districts Manual (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - History of Activities - Zoning Digest (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - PAS (Planning Advisory Service) (Engineering News - Record) (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - PAS: History (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - PAS: Promotion (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - PAS: Subscription cost chargeable to HUD (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Zoning Digest: History (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Zoning Digest: Promotion (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Zoning Flood Plain: Zoning and Insurance (Box 24, Folder 45-47)
  - Zoning: correspondence, clippings, and ordinances (Box 24, Folder 48-49)
  - ASPO-AIP Program coordination: Joint Program in National Affairs (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - ASPO-AIP-NAHRO meetings (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - ASPO-AIP-NAHRO meeting: Gettysburg, Pa., 1968 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - National Conference on Outdoor Recreation Organization and Program, 1924-1925, 1925 (Box 25)
  - Report of the Planning Board, Wakefield, Mass., 1925 (Box 25)
  - Zoning for Manchester, 1926 (Box 25)
  - The Use of Deed Restriction in Subdivision Development, 1928 (Box 25)
  - City Plan of the City of White Plains, New York, 1928 (Box 25)
  - The Civic Development Plans of Alton Illinois, 1928 (Box 25)
  - The Piscatagua Regional Defense Area of New Hampshire and Maine, 1942 (Box 25)
  - Rebuilding Providence Annual Report, 1948 (Box 25)
  - State Government, 1950 (Box 25)
  - City Planning and Landscape Architecture at the University of Illinois - An Historical Record (1868-1954), 1954 (Box 25)
  - Making it Work: The Housing Facilitator Study Report, 1973 (Box 25)
  - Joint Housing Obstacles, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Housing for the Miami Valley Region, 1974 (Box 25)
  - An Affirmative Fair and Equal Housing Plan for the Miami Valley Region, 1974 (Box 25)
- Series V. Files of Dennis O'Harrow (including materials regarding a book and memorial dedicated to O'Harrow)
  - Master plan - Subdivision Ordinance and Zoning Ordinance of Dune Acres, Indiana, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "A Place for Everything," Bowdoin College - Maine Coast, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1963-66 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1959, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1955-61 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1960-62 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1963-67 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1956-62 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - O'Harrow Speeches, 1966-67 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - O'Harrow - ASPO time summaries (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - O'Harrow papers (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - O'Harrow articles: "When 100 Families Move In" (editorial) - reprinted in St. Louis Post-Dispatch (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - "For Margaret O'Harrow" (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - O'Harrow Memorabilia (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Fund, A-E (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Fund, F-J (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Fund, K-O (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Fund, P-T (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Fund, U-Z (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Dennis O'Harrow (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Committee - reports and correspondence (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - O'Harrow - African Study Tour (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - O'Harrow - Screening Committee successor to O'Harrow (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - O'Harrow gift (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - O'Harrow - death (Box 26, Folder 25-29)
  - O'Harrow Memorial Fund - contributions (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - O'Harrow, 1948-50 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - O'Harrow, 1951-52 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - O'Harrow, 1953-54 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - O'Harrow, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - O'Harrow, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - O'Harrow, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - O'Harrow, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - O'Harrow, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - O'Harrow, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - O'Harrow, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - O'Harrow, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - O'Harrow, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - O'Harrow, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - O'Harrow, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - O'Harrow, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - O'Harrow, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper clippings, miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Park Forest (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - "Notations" (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation Grant (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - ASPO data (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Procedure and publisher correspondence (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Book miscellany (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Consulting: Babbitt, Bismark, New York, Wauwatosa (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - O'Harrow, 1953 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - O'Harrow, 1954 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - O'Harrow, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - O'Harrow, 1956-57 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - O'Harrow, 1958 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - O'Harrow, 1959-60 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - O'Harrow, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - O'Harrow, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - O'Harrow, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 34-35)
  - O'Harrow, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - O'Harrow, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - O'Harrow, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - O'Harrow, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - O'Harrow source material (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Source material - churches (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bismark - consulting (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - O'Harrow invitations, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Source material - articles, meeting invitations, etc. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Miscellany not used - photos, newsclips, extra copies, etc. (Box 28, Folder 9-11)
  - Bibliography draft (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Table of contents (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Award citations (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Biography data and awards (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Biography data - source material (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Preface and Introduction (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 1 - What planning is --- and is not (Box 28, Folder 18-22)
  - Chapter 2 - Scylla the Bathwater and Other Pitfalls (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Reprints - 100 Families (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 3 - Laws and Prophecies (Box 28, Folder 25-26)
  - Chapter 4 - What This Country Needs is --- (land) (Box 28, Folder 27-28)
  - Chapter 4 - What This Country Needs is --- (transportation) (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Chapter 4 - What This Country Needs is --- (techniques) (Box 28, Folder 31-35)
  - Chapter 6 - Communicating (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Chapter 6 - Zoning (Box 29, Folder 1-4)
  - Chapter 7 - About Planners (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - Marjorie S. Berger - personal (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
  - Mailing list - contributors to O'Harrow Memorial Fund, 1968-69 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Drafts for chapters of Dennis O'Harrow: Plan Talk and Plain Talk edited by Marjorie Berger - Table of contents and Introduction, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 1 - Edited pages 1-39 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 1 - Edited pages 40-73 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 2 - Edited pages 1-50 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 3 - Edited pages 1-30 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 1-33 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 34-54 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 54-82 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 83-112 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 113-143 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 144-212 (omitted) (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 213-242 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 4 - Edited pages 243-274 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 5 - Edited pages 1-27 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 6 - Edited pages 1-35 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Chapter 6 - Edited pages 36-60 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Chapter 6 - Edited pages 61-97 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Chapter 7 - Edited pages 1-43 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Chapter 7 - Edited pages 44-88 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Note cards (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Series VI. ASPO honorary life members files
  - Honorary Life Members - missing files (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Life Member (in error) - Abendroth, Fred J. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Life Member #181 - Adams, Fred J. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Honorary Life Member #178 - Agle, Charles K. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Honorary Life Member #168 - Allred, R. Clay (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Life Member #134 - Anderson, William (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Honorary Life Member #102 - Antonacci, Michael H. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Honorary Life Member #51 - Ascher, Charles S. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Honorary Life Member #131 - Atwood, Edwin E. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Life Member #172 - Bagby, Scott (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Life Member #104 - Bailey, Russell D. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Life Member #13 - Bartholomew, Harland (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Bartlett, Terrell (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Honorary Life Member #95 - Berg, Carl E. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Honorary Life Member #180 - Berger, Marjorie (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Honorary Life Member #174 - Blessing, Charles A. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Life Member #58 - Blucher, Walter H. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Honorary Life Member #40 - Blumenfeld, Hans (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Honorary Life Member #14 - Brainerd, Harry B. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Honorary Life Member #170 - Breese, Gerald (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Honorary Life Member #54 - Breivogel, Milton (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Honorary Life Member #188 - Chamales, Christopher John (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Life Member #155 - Claire, William H. (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Honorary Life Member #145 - Clarenbach, Fred A. (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Honorary Life Member #60 - Cline, Arthur R. (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Honorary Life Member #126 - Cotter, Vernon S. (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Honorary Life Member #156 - Davey, William E. (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Honorary Life Member #85 - Dieter, Frank (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Honorary Life Member #72 - Dill, Malcolm H. (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Honorary Life Member #121 - Doyle, Sidney E. (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Honorary Life Member #169 - Dumoulin, Rockwell King (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Honorary Life Member #108 - Eisner, Simon (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Honorary Life Member #144 - Eldredge, H. Wentworth (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Honorary Life Member #142 - Ellifrit, Ralph S. (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Honorary Life Member #69 - Emery, George F. (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Honorary Life Member #96 - Faludi, E.G. (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Honorary Life Member #86 - Faure, Andre M. (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Honorary Life Member #124 - Feiss, Carl (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Honorary Life Member #137 - Fernbach, Richard B. (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Honorary Life Member #109 - Fisher, Howard T. (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Honorary Life Member #185 - Fraser, Earl D. (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Honorary Life Member #75 - Gardner, Carl L. (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Honorary Life Member #88 - Gimre, Gerald S. (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Honorary Life Member #105 - Gould, Harry B. (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Honorary Life Member #171 - Gray, Aelred, J. (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Honorary Life Member #107 - Gray, Katharine Meeker (Box 30, Folder 46)
  - Honorary Life Member #177 - Haring, Tibor J. (Box 30, Folder 47)
  - Honorary Life Member #91 - Harral, Henry D. (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Honorary Life Member #89 - Hawkins, Charles W. (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Honorary Life Member #153 - Hayward, George C. (Box 30, Folder 50)
  - Honorary Life Member #2 - Hetherton, P.C. (Box 30, Folder 51)
  - Honorary Life Member #0 - Hirsh, Morris Henry (Box 30, Folder 52)
  - Honorary Life Member #123 - Bach, Ira J. (Box 30, Folder 53)
  - Honorary Life Member #97 - Hoben, Edmond H. (Box 30, Folder 54)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Horwitz, Aaron B. (Box 30, Folder 55)
  - Honorary Life Member #162 - Howard, John T. (Box 30, Folder 56)
  - Honorary Life Member #186 - Hoyt, Robert Ingle (Box 30, Folder 57)
  - Honorary Life Member #157 - Hubbard, Leonard F. (Box 30, Folder 58)
  - Honorary Life Member #59 - Hyde, John W. (Box 30, Folder 59)